Guide to the Arena Stage records, 1950-2007
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Arena Stage records
1950-2007
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
Arena Stage
C0017
394.15 linear feet (675 boxes)
The Arena Stage records consists of material that span the theater's 60 year history including production notebooks, photographs, audiotapes, videotpaes, playbills, scrapbooks, scripts, handwritten correspondence, and other production materials.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Arena Stage in 2000-2008.
Historical Information
Arena Stage was an early leader in the resident theater movement. One of the first not-for-profit theaters in the United States as well as a pioneer of the regional theater movement the Arena Stage was the first regional theater to transfer a production to Broadway, the first invited by the U.S. State Department to tour behind the Iron Curtain and the first to receive a Tony Award. Co-founded in 1950 by Edward Mangum a teacher from the George Washington University, and Zelda Fichandler, one of his students, Arena Stage was opened in Washington D.C. to fill the void left by the closing of the National Theater in 1948. Deriving it's name from the idea of "theater in the round," Arena Stage became one of the first resident theaters in the United States, beginning with a company of only eight actors. Today, Arena performs to over 250,000 patrons during a September to June season and employs nearly 200 theater professionals and craftpersons, who are responsible for all the costumes and scenery seen on stage. Many now- famous actors took part in Arena Stage productions during the early part of their careers. Some of them include Robert Prosky, Morgan Freeman, Dianne Weist, James Earl Jones, Kevin Kline, Christopher Guest, Yeardly Smith and Samuel L. Jackson.
Scope and Content
The Arena Stage records consists of material that span the theater's 60 year history including production notebooks, photographs, audiotapes, videotpaes, playbills, scrapbooks, scripts, handwritten correspondence, and other production materials.
Arrangement
Arranged by document type.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Special Collections and Archives holds other theatre collections.
Index Terms
Corporate Names:
Arena Stage (Organization: Washington, D.C.)
Subjects:
Theater--Washington (D.C.)
Document Types:
Photographic prints.; Sound recordings.; Video recordings.
Contents List
- Arena Stage Theatre Communications Group files, 1950-2000; 1.5 linear ft. (3 boxes)
  Materials include information from the Arena Stage`s work with the Theater Communications Group.
  - 30th Anniversary, general (Box 1, Folder 1)
    file containes information of general plans for celebrating and promoting the Arena Stage's 30th anniversary season, 1980
  - Three Institutions project, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    file containes general information on the Three Institutions project. The projects aims was to gain federal assistance for the Arena Stage, Folger Shakespear Library and Theatre and the Corcoran Art Museaum
  - Three Institutions project, misc. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Three Institutions project, misc. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Theatre Rental, 1960's - 1970's (Box 1, Folder 5)
    file containes correspondence and information regarding the renting of Arena Stage facilities for outside use.
  - Theater Study for Congress (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "Tabs" publications (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Folder containes 4 issues of "Tabs"; Vol. 28 No. 3 (Sept. 1970), Vol. 27 No. 1 (March 1969), Vol. 26 No. 4 (Dec. 1968), Vol. 31 No. 3 (Sept. 1973, 100th number)
  - Telephone proposal, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    file contains information on potential change of telephone service
  - Misc. Theatre Communications Group publications (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Theater Communications Group infromation on the potential use of Cable Television (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Theater Development Fund, general information (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Theatre Communications Group, Managers Bulletin (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Theatre Communications Group board (Box 3, Folder 1)
    contains general information on the TCG's board
  - TCG - Financial Summary (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - TCG - General information 1 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - TCG - General Information 2 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - TCG - general file 1 of 3 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - TCG - general file 2 of 3 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - TCG - general file 3 of 3 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Arena Stage stage manager reports, 1950-2000; 9 linear ft. (11 boxes)
  Collection contains the stage managers reports for most productions between 1950-2000.
  - Stage Manager's report: After the Fall; '79-'80 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ah Wilderness! 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - All the Kings Men, 1987-188 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Buffalo; 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - American Splendor, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - An American Tragedy 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Andersonville trial; 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Animal Cracker 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Acent of Mt. Fuji 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - As You Like It '83-'84 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Autumn Garden '76-'77 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Awake and Sing; 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Beyond Therapy '83-'84 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Billy Bishop Goes to War (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Blood Knot (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Boccaccio (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Briar Patch 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Candide 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Casualties 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Catsplay 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Checkmates 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - The Chemmy Circle 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - The Cherry Orchard 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - The Cherry Orchard 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - The Child 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - A Chorus of Disapproval 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Cloud 9 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Cocoanuts 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Cold Storage 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Comedians 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Conflict of Interest 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Conquest of the South Pole 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Crime and Punishment 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - The Crucible 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - The Crucible 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - curse of the starving class 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Cymbeline 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Dance of Death 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Dandelion Wine 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Death of a Salesman (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - A Delicate Balance 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Design for Living 79-80 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Disability: A Comedy 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Disability 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Don Juan 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Duck hunting 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - The Dubbuk 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Edith Stein 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Emigres 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Enchanted Night/The Police (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Enemies 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Enemy of the People 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Enrico IV 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Execution of Justice 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Fences 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Hamlet: restricted correspondence; 1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Forever Yours; 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Foursome 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Front Page 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Front Page 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Galileo 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Gemini 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Geniuses 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Glass Menagerie 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Glen Gary Glen Ross 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - God Bless You, Mr. Rosewater 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Good Person of Setzuan 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Gospel at Colonus 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Great White Hope 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Hamlet 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Happy End 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Heart Break House 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Heart Break House 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - History of the American Film 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - The Hostage 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - The House of Blue Leaves 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Idiots Delight 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - The Immigrant 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - The Importance of Being Ernest 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - School for Wives 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Separations 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Serjeant Musgraves Dance 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Sign in Sidney/Brustein's Window 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Singers 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Six Characters in Search of an Author 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - The Skin of our Teeth 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Stand-up Tragedy 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Starting here, Starting Now 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Status Quo Vadis 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Still Life 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Stray Dogs 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Streamers 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - A Street Car Named Desire 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - The Suicide 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Tales from the Vienna Woods 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - The Taming of the Shrew 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Tartuffe 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Terbele and Her Demon 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - The Tenth Man 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Three Men on a Horse 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Three Sisters 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Tin Types 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Tom 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Tom Foolery 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - The TOT Family 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Trappers 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Tricks 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Twelfth Night 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Undiscovered Country 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Uptight 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Waiting for Godot 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - A Walk in the Woods 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - What the Butler Saw 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Whos Afraid of Virginia Wolf? 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - The Wild Duck 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - The Winter's Tale 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Wipe Out Games 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Living Stage production reports 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Living Stage production reports 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - "images", script 1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - "Longstreet", script 1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - "Images", production materials (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - "Every Heart in the House", production information (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Room Service 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Ruling Class 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Saint Joan 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - A Public Prosecutor is Sick of it All 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Pueblo 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - A Raisin in the Sun 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Saturday, Sunday and Monday 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - K-2 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Inherit the Wind 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - The Inspector General 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Isn't it Romantic? (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Julius Ceaser 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Arturo Ui (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Restoration 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Ring Around the Moon 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Rivers and Ravines 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Major Barbara 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Major Barbara 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Madmen 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - The Magistrate (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Lower Depths 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - MacBeth 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Lessons From Aloes 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Light up the Sky 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Living at Home 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Look Back in Anger 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Loose Ends 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Long Days Journey into Night 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - The Last Meeting of the Knights of the White Magnolia 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Leonce and Lena 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Les Blancs 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - The Lesson 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Juno and the Paycock 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Mother Courage 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Measure for Measure (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Marriage of Bette and Boo 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Prospect Mortality 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Exhibition,Scooping 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Poor Bitos (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Plenty 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Playboy of the West Indies 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Plays and other Plays 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Merrily We Roll Along 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - A Mid-Summers Nights Dream 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Moonchildren 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Passion Play 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Pantomime 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Our Town (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Pantagleize 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - On the Town 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Ourselves Alone 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Our Town 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - The Piggy Bank 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - The Philadelphia Storey 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Nothing Sacred 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Oba Kosa 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - One Flew Over the Cookoos Nest (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Once in a Lifetime 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Old Times 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Of Thee I Sing 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Man Who Came to Dinner 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Man and Superman 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Nightclub Cantata (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Night Mother (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - The Night Thoreau Spent in Jail 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - The 1940's Radio Hour (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - No Place to Be Somebody 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Molly Sweeney 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - A Month in the Country 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Mrs. Klein 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - My Children, My Africa 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - The Odessey 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Of Thee I Sing 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Our Town 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - A Perfect Ganesh 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Playquest 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - The Plough and the Stars 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - The Price 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Pygmalion 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - The Revengers Comedies 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - A Room of One's Own 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Room Service 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Seagull 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - She Stoops to Conquer 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Skin of our Teeth 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Small World 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Sunday in the Park with George 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Summer and Smoke 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Twelfth Night 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Trinidad Sisters 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Touch of the Poet 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - The Time of Your Life 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - What the Bulter Saw 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Wonderful Life 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Yerma 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - You Can't Take it With You 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Way of the World 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Waiting Room 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Voir-Dire 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Vivisections of the Blown Mind 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - The Visit 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Uncle Vanya 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Teen Mom 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Misc. production reports 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - misc. production 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - misc. reports 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - misc. production reports 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Children First 1996 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - misc. production reports 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - production reports 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Banjo Dancing 1981 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Babes in Boyland - S.M. reports (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Before it Hits Home 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Blues for an Alabama Sky 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Born Guilty 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Brother's Karamazov (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Candide 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Cerceau 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Community Carol 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Dance of Death 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Dacning at Lugnasa 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - A Doll House 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Dimly Perceived Threats to the System 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Dirty Work 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Ghosts 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Hedda Gabler 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - House Arrests 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - I Am a Man 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - It Ain't Nothing but the Blues 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - It's the Truth if you Thing it is 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Jar the Floor 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Long Day's Journey into Night 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Lovers and Executioners 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Matchmaker 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Misalliance 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - The Miser 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Arena Stage scrapbooks, 1949-1987; 33 linear ft. (11 boxes)
  The collection contains bound binders containing press clippings, photographs, and Arena Stage promotional materials. Of particular interst are three scrapbooks on the Arena Stages 1973 tour of Russia.
  - 1949 - July 1951 (Box 1, Volume 1)
  - August 1951- August 1952 (Box 1, Volume 2)
  - August 1952 - August 1953 (Box 1, Volume 3)
  - August 1953 - August 1954 (Box 1, Volume 4)
  - September 1954 - June 1955 (Box 1, Volume 5)
  - September 1956 - August 1957 (Box 1, Volume 6)
  - September 1957 - August 1958 (Box 1, Volume 7)
  - September 1960 - February 1961 (Box 2, Volume 1)
  - March 1961 - August 1961 (Box 2, Volume 2)
  - August 1961 - January 1962 (Box 2, Volume 3)
  - February 1962 - September 1962 (Box 2, Volume 4)
  - August 1962 - February 1963 (Box 2, Volume 5)
  - March 1962 - September 1963 (Box 2, Volume 6)
  - September 1963 - February 1964 (Box 3, Volume 1)
  - March 1964 - September 1964 (Box 3, Volume 2)
  - September 1964 - February 1965 (Box 3, Volume 3)
  - March 1965 - October 1965 (Box 3, Volume 4)
  - September 1965 - January 1966 (Box 3, Volume 5)
  - February 1966 - June 1966 (Box 3, Volume 6)
  - August 1966 - February 1967 (Box 4, Volume 1)
  - March 1967 - August 1967 (Box 4, Volume 2)
  - August 1967 - January 1968 (Box 4, Volume 3)
  - 1967-1968 The Great White Hope (Box 4, Volume 4)
  - Februdary 1968 - August 1968 (Box 4, Volume 5)
  - June 1968 - July 1969 (Box 4, Volume 5)
  - June 1975 - February 1976 (Box 5, Volume 1)
  - March 1976 - July 1976 (Box 5, Volume 2)
  - 1975 - 1976 Tony Award (Box 5, Volume 3)
  - August 1976 - January 1977 (Box 5, Volume 4)
  - February 1977 - July 1977 (Box 5, Volume 5)
  - August 1977 - January 1978 (Box 5, Volume 6)
  - February 1978 - July 1978 (Box 5, Volume 7)
  - August 1978 - January 1979 (Box 6, Volume 1)
  - February 1979 - August 1979 (Box 6, Volume 2)
  - August 1979 - December1979 (Box 6, Volume 3)
  - January 1980 - July 1980 (Box 6, Volume 4)
  - August 1980 - December 1980 (Box 6, Volume 5)
  - January 1981 - April 1981 (Box 6, Volume 6)
  - May 1981 - August 1981 (Box 6, Volume 7)
  - September 1981 - December 1981 (Box 7, Volume 1)
  - Janurary 1982 - May 1982 (Box 7, Volume 2)
  - June 1982 - August 1982 (Box 7, Volume 3)
  - September 1982 - December 1982 (Box 7, Volume 4)
  - January 1983 - April 1983 (Box 7, Volume 5)
  - May 1983 - September 1983 (Box 7, Volume 6)
  - October 1983 - December 1983 (Box 7, Volume 7)
  - January - March 1984 (Box 8, Volume 1)
  - April 1984 - June 1984 (Box 8, Volume 2)
  - June 1984 - November 1984 (Box 8, Volume 3)
  - December 1984 - February 1985 (Box 8, Volume 4)
  - March - May 1985 (Box 8, Volume 5)
  - June - September 1985 (Box 8, Volume 6)
  - October - December 1985 (Box 8, Volume 7)
  - September 1958 - July 1959 (Box 9, Volume 1)
  - August 1959 - January 1960 (Box 9, Volume 2)
  - February 1960 - August 1960 (Box 9, Volume 3)
  - June 1969 - August 1970 (Box 9, Volume 4)
  - September 1970 - August 1971 (Box 9, Volume 5)
  - January - March 1986 (Box 10, Volume 1)
  - April - July 1986 (Box 10, Volume 2)
  - July - September 1986 (Box 10, Volume 3)
  - October - December 1986 (Box 10, Volume 4)
  - January - March 1987 (Box 10, Volume 5)
  - March 1987 - May 1987 (Box 10, Volume 6)
  - misc 1950's (Box 11, Volume 1)
  - Russia Tour book 1, 1973 (Box 11, Volume 2)
  - Russia Tour book 2, 1973 (Box 11, Volume 3)
  - photographic record of Arena Stages history (Box 11, Volume 4)
  - photos of visitors to the theatre (Box 11, Volume 5)
  - Russian Tour book 3, 1973 (Box 11, Volume 6)
  - misc. Arena Stage mailings and promotion items (Box 11, Volume 7)
- Arena Stage production photograph books, 1960-1999; 4.5 linear ft. (15 boxes)
  Collection contains bound photo books of individual Arena Stage productions including the 1973 produciton of Inherit the Wind performed in Russian.
  - The Devils 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Don Juan 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Dybbuk 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Emigres 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Emigres 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - An Enemy of the People 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Galileo 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Galileo 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Gemini 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Gemini 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Geniuses 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - God Bless you, Mr. Rosewater 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Hamlet 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Heartbreak House (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - A History of the American Film 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Hotel Paradiso 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Imaginary Invalid 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Imaginary Invalide 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Indians 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Idiots Delight 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Idiots Delight 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Julius Caeser 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Kean 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - K2 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - A Lesson from Aloes 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - A Lie of the Mind 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Long Day's Journey into Night 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Loose Ends 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - The Lower Depths 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - The Madness of God 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Major Barbara 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - The Man Who Came to Dinner 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - The Moon in the Yellow River 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - A Midsummer's Nights Dream 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - A Midsummers Nights Dream 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - The National Health 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Nightculb Cantata 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Once in a Lifetime 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Once in a Lifetime 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - One More time 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - On the Razzle (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Pantomime 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Passion Play 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - The Persecution and Assassination of Jean-Paul Marat 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - The Persecution and Assassination of Jean-Paul Marat 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Six Character in Search of an Author 1968-1969 (Box 10)
    Loose in box.
  - Screen Play 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Serjeant Musgrave's Dance 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Sejeant Musgraves Dance 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Streamers 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 2)